Day 33.
Minimum viable product.
Here we go.
It's just the simplest way for you to test an idea of a product or service
with the least possible investment in time and money in it.
Here I created an idea.
The idea will work.
I don't know but the best way for me to test it is within my own framework.
Who wants my cigarette here?
Or because it's the people who are warmer here.
To buy your product,
test it here and then open the market.
Oi Milene worries.
No actually it's 1 New project.
If you have 1 little time,
it's going to be nice,
I don't need a customer in the old real,
I just need 1 Person from that label to accept.
She Said Look
strategy.
The secret is not making money from the client,
but through him.
Bro
go for the soft hour brother caraca mano the truffles are flying here eh?
Mano vixe only left that.
Nine I need to fuel that I said.
Nice guy is a good strategy but is it the best strategy
for those saved to give you an idea?
Like if a marketing agency I can bring solutions to
the places you want to go what's your difficulty?
It's prospecting but improving the base.
Like I didn't come to get it out of the safe,
I came to add the safe.
You know what I need is to lure forward,
right? Bro?
Let me put together a strategic plan.
I present you.
See what you think?
And then in the meantime I'm making my truffle farms.
is on
make yourself comfortable with it.
If the guy isn't even able to talk that he's serving a lot of people,
that's a very good sign because he has a very large flow of people.
Is it on there?
With more demand more truffle sale.
License so you can have a quality product at your coffee barbershop here.
The guy has a truffle
cuzão Cara now zeroed my truffle of New my bro
the money comes in.
A visa on the plan
until tomorrow.